Where's Reiju?
أين ريجو؟
Who knows? She went out earlier.
لا أعلم، غادرَتْ قبل قليل
♪ Tea! ♪
♪ شاي ♪
♪ Green tea! ♪
♪ شاي أخضر ♪
♪ Which would you like to have? ♪
♪ أيهما تريد؟ ♪
Anyway, Father, where will Sanji and his wife live after they get married?
بأي حال يا أبي، أين سيقيم سانجي وزوجته بعد الزواج؟
In Germa, of course.
في جيرما بالطبع
If we don't hold her as a hostage, we don't know what they'll demand hereafter.
إن لم نأسرها، فلا نعلم ما قد يطالبون به في المستقبل
We're dealing with pirates.
نحن نتعامل مع قراصنة
I see. A hostage, huh?
فهمت، نأسرها إذًا؟
Maybe they'll want to hold Sanji hostage too, in case something happens, y'know?
قد يأسرون سانجي أيضًا في حال حدث شيء ما، صحيح؟
Don't be stupid, Niji.
كفاك حماقة يا نيجي
Even if they do that, would killing Sanji matter to us?
حتى لو فعلوا ذلك، فهل سيغضبنا قتلهم لسانجي؟
You're right.
أنت مُحق
It wouldn't!
إطلاقًا
I can't wait...
...لا أطيق الانتظار
to live with Sanji again.
للعيش بمقربة من سانجي مجدّدًا
Please! Don't do it!
أرجوكِ لا تفعلي هذا
I don't wanna be eaten!
لا أريد أن أُؤكل
You guys are hungry, aren't you?
أنتم جائعون يا رفاق، صحيح؟
We're starving!
نحن نتضور جوعًا
This will be the finest game dish ever.
ستكون أفضل طريدة تُقدم لكم على الإطلاق
Don't... D-D-Don't eat me!
لا... لا تأكلوني
– Let me down! – Just give up already.
أنزليني يجدر بكِ أن تسلّمي نفسكِ للأمر الواقع
Brûlée has sealed her own downfall.
أفعال بروليه أودتها للتهلكة بنفسها
What? What?!
ماذا؟ ماذا؟
The Carrot that got caught with me at that time was a fake.
كاروت التي قُبض عليها معي في ذلك الوقت كانت نسخة مزيفة
It's a frog that was transformed into a mirror image of Carrot by Brûlée's ability.
إنّه ضفدع تم تحويله إلى نسخة مطابقة لكاروت بقدرة بروليه
The real Carrot...
...كاروت الحقيقية
is in the attic.
في العليَّة
Stop! Don't eat me!
توقفي لا تأكلوني
Please! Help! Chobro!
أنقذني يا تشونيكي
Help me!
أنقذني
But... I feel bad for the frog.
ولكنني أشعر بالأسى على الضفدع
There are 16 enemies in this house.
ثمة 16 عدو في هذا المنزل
The most troubling ones are Randolph, Aristocroc,
أكثر من أخشاهم هم: راندولف والتمساح النبيل
the mysterious chimney man Diesel,
ورجل مدخنة القطار الغامض ديزل
and... Brûlée.
وكذلك بروليه
My only chance to catch them off guard...
...فرصتي الوحيدة لمباغتتهم
is the moment they drop the fake Carrot.
هي في اللحظة التي يُسقطون فيها كاروت المزيفة
Randolph, cut the rope.
راندولف، اقطع الحبل
Okay.
عُلم
She's gonna freak out when she gets dropped in. I'll put the lid on right away.
ستفقد صوابها حالما تقع في القدر لذا الأفضل أن أضع الغطاء فورًا
Here goes, Madame Brûlée!
سأقطع الحبل يا بروليه-ساما
Now! Carrot!
الآن يا كاروت
Uh-huh!
أجل
Winding up and...
...أحكم قبضتي ومن ثم
What are you doing, Randolph?
ماذا تفعل يا راندولف؟
Madame Brûlée, someone came down from the attic!
بروليه-ساما، أحدهم نزل من العليَّة
What?!
ماذا؟
There are two rabbit girls!
ثمة اثنتان من الفتاة الأرنبة
Good!
جيّد
Calm down! Hey!
اهدأ
Hurry up, Carrot!
بسرعة يا كاروت
You can count on me, Chobro!
أعتمد عليّ يا تشونيكي
What is she gonna do?
ما الذي ستفعله؟
Randolph! Just cut the rope!
راندولف، اقطع الحبل بسرعة
O-Okay!
حـ-حاضر
Carrot!
كاروت
Take this!
ها أنا ذا
What?!
ماذا؟
Oh, no! You can't do that! No!
هذا خطير لا تفعلي هذا كلا
Nooo!
كــلا
– Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! – Madame Brûlée!
حار حار - بروليه-ساما -
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow...
...حار حار حار
Ouch! Ouch!
حار حار
All right!
جيّد
Rumble!
رامبل
– Madame Brûlée! – This is bad news!
بروليه-ساما - إنها مصيبة -
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
حار حار حار حار
Oh, no!
مصيبة
Madame Brûlée!
بروليه-ساما
Electrical Luna!
القمر الكهربائي
This is bad! I gotta tell Mama!
مصيبة، سأخبر ماما
Leave it to me, Chobro!
دع أمره لي يا تشونيكي
Choo-choo! Choo-choo! Choo-choo and choo-choo and choo!
صوت قطار
Idiots! No one can catch up with me once I start running...
...أحمقان ليس بمقدور أحد مجاراتي حينما أركض
Ouch!
مؤلم
Garchu!
غارتشو
What?!
ماذا؟
Guess who?
احزر من أكون؟
No, no, no... Let go of me!
كلا، كلا، دعيني
Not yet!
ليس بعد
I said "Let go of me"!
أخبرتك أن تدعيني
Okay.
حسنًا
What?
ماذا؟
I-I'm gonna crash!
سأصطدم
I can't stop!
لا يمكنني الوقوف
There!
ها أنت ذا
Yes! We beat Brûlée's group!
مرحى هزمنا مجموعة بروليه
Chobro!
تشونيكي
Alright!
جيّد
Now we can use Brûlée's ability to jump in and out of the mirrors!
بات بإمكاننا الآن استخدام قدرة بروليه للدخول والخروج من المرايا
Let's travel in this dimension across the island to look for everyone!
فلنذهب عبر هذا البعد حول الجزيرة للعثور على رفاقنا
May I come in-nasu ?
أيمكنني الدخول-ناسو؟
Yeah.
أجل
Thank you for going shopping.
شكرًا على التسوّق
No problem-nasu.
إنّه واجبي-ناسو
Um, I've got some news-nasu.
ثمة أخبار لك-ناسو
We're currently holding Straw Hat Luffy and the Cat Burglar captive-nasu.
إننا نحتجز قبعة القش والقطة السارقة حاليًّا-ناسو
They captured Luffy and Nami-san ?
أَسَروا لوفي ونامي-سان؟
As long as you don't try to run away, everything will work out just fine, Sanji.
ما دمت لن تهرب، فكل شيء سيسير على ما يرام يا سانجي
And a male mink and Soul King are still rampaging.
ورجل مينك وملك السول ما زالا يسببان الفوضى
Brook!
بروك
Sweet Commander Smoothie and Baron Tamago went to subdue them-nasu,
قائدة الحلوى سموذي-ساما والبارون تاماغو غادرا لقمعهما-ناسو
but they're still struggling to...
ولكنهما ما يزالان صامدان
That's enough.
هذا يكفي
Can I have my groceries?
أيمكنك إعطائي ما طلبته منك؟
Yeah, here they are-nasu.
أجل، تفضل-ناسو
Note: "Nasu" = Eggplant.
باذنجان = ناسو
If you're hungry, I can bring you something, like nasu.
يمكنني جلب الباذنجان إن كنتَ جائعًا
No, thanks.
لا حاجة لذلك
Can I use this kitchen?
أيمكنني استخدام هذا المطبخ؟
What?
ماذا؟
Pudding-chan didn't show up for that last meal, so I'll cook something for her.
لم تحضر بودينغ-تشان على مائدة العشاء، لذا سأطبخ من أجلها
I see-nasu.
هكذا إذًا-ناسو
I'm worried about her.
إنني قلق عليها
Yes, I heard that she still doesn't feel well-nasu...
أجل، سمعت أن صحتها ما زالت سيئة-ناسو
These are the keys.
ها هم المفاتيح
Pedro-san ! I'll do it!
بيدرو-سان، سأفعلها حتمًا
Damn you!
سحقًا لك
How dare you do that!
أنى لك فعل هذا؟
I have to do it!
لم يكن لديّ خيار آخر
Swallow Banderole!
ابتلاع الشريط
I asked my partner to risk his life before I came here!
طلبتُ من شريكي المخاطرة بحياته قبل مجيئي إلى هنا
I have to get what I need...
يجب أن أحصل على مرادي
or I'll lose face!
وإلا سأخسر وجهي أمامه
What do you mean, "I don't have a face to lose"?!
من قال أنني لا أمتلك وجهًا؟
Guards, can you hear me?
أيمكنكم سماعي أيها الحرس؟
Answer!
أجيبوني
I've got to hurry.
يجب أن أسرع
Is the intruder in there?!
هل الدخيل هناك؟
Mama! You didn't have to come! I can handle this!
ماما، لم يكن عليك القدوم، يمكنني التعامل مع الوضع
Get out of my way, Smoothie!
ابتعدي عن طريقي يا سموذي
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Don't you know whose treasure
...ألا تعرف لمن تعود
you're messing with?!
هذه الكنوز التي تعبث بها؟
Don't tell me it's...
...أيعقل أنّها
Big Mom!
بيغ مام؟
Oh? What a strange creature!
يا لك من مخلوق غريب
The intruder is passing through the hallway near the courtyard!
الدخيل يمر من خلال الرواق القريب من الباحة
Corner him from both sides!
حاصروه من كِلا الطرفين
All hands, shields up!
ارفعوا الدروع جميعًا
Charge!
هجوم
Almost there!
كدنا نصل
Alright! We cornered him in the courtyard!
جيّد، حاصرناه في الباحة
Damn! What are they up to?
سحقًا، ما الذي ينوون فعله؟
It's been a while-bon !
مضت فترة طويلة-بون
Baron Tamago!
البارون تاماغو
Captain Pedro of the Nox Pirates!
قبطان طاقم قراصنة نوكس، بيدرو
Although you're my enemy, I've always respected you.
رغم أنّك عدوي، إلا أنني أحترمك
And now that we're facing one another,
في كل مرة نتقابل بها
the scars on our left eyes both twitch-toi-et-moi.
نتذكر هذا الندب الموجود على العين اليسرى لكلٍ منا
Five years ago, you really held on to your life.
لقد تمسكت بالحياة بشدة قبل خمسة سنوات
Why have you returned?
فلِمَ عُدت مجدّدًا؟
You don't have much time left to live-soufflé.
ليس لديك متّسع من الوقت لتعيشه-سوفليه
On that day, Mama took...
...في ذلك اليوم، ماما سلبت منك
50 years of your life-bon !
خمسين عام من حياتك
Yes, I know that.
أجل، أعلم ذلك
I'm not...
...ولا
expecting to go home alive!
أتوقع عودتي للوطن حيًّا
Sanji!
سانجي
Not here!
ليس هنا
Oh, there's a ghost!
شبح
Not here, either.
ليس هنا أيضًا
Is it farther ahead?
هل المكان أبعد؟
Wake up, Brûlée!
استيقظي يا بروليه
Where is the mirror that leads to Whole Cake Chateau?
أين المرآة المؤدية إلى قصر الكعكة الكاملة؟
Diesel! Do you know where to go?!
ديزل، ألا تعرف مكانها؟
How would I know?! Dammit!
كيف لي أن أعرف؟ سحقًا
As long as we're touching Brûlée, we can jump in and out of the mirrors!
طالما نحن نلمس بروليه، يمكننا الدخول والخروج من المرايا
This dimension is connected to the mirrors all across Whole Cake Island.
هذا البُعد مرتبط بالمرايا المؤدية إلى جزيرة الكعكة الكاملة
We should've reached the castle already.
ينبغي أننا وصلنا إلى القصر سلفًا
Brûlée! Wake up!
بروليه، استيقظي
C'mon!
هيّا
Anyway, we gotta try to find it ourselves until she wakes up!
علي أيّ حال، علينا أن نحاول العثور على تلك المرآة حتّى تستيقظ
Let's keep going until we find it!
فلنتابع حتّى نعثر عليها
You guys will pay for this!
ستدفعون ثمن هذا
Stop it, Luffy! What are you doing?!
توقف يا لوفي ما الذي تُفكر فيه؟
It's no use...
لا فائدة
If you don't stop, you're going to rip off your hands!
ستتمزق يداك إن لم تكفّ عن هذا
That's what I'm trying to do!
هذا ما أحاول فعله
What?!
ماذا؟
No! Don't do it!
كلا كفّ عن هذا
I have no choice!
لا خيارَ أمامي
Is there any other way to get us out of here?!
أثمّة وسيلة أخرى للخروج من هنا؟
Isn't it better to have your arms torn apart...
أليس أهون عليكِ أن تتمزق يداك على أن تموتي هنا؟
A little more to go!
القليل بعد
No, no, no! They're getting thinner than before!
هذا سيئ أصبحَتْ يداك أشد نحافة من السابق
That's what I want!
هذا ما أريده
While we're hoping for someone to come help,
...بينما نحن جالسان هنا ننتظر قدوم أحدٍ لمساعدتنا
we'll lose everything, and eventually get killed by Big Mom!
سنخسر كلّ شيء وتقتلنا بيغ مام
That's so stupid! I don't wanna die like that!
هذا سخيف، لا أريد الموت هكذا
Tear yours apart, too!
اقطعي أطرافك أنتِ أيضًا
What?! Are you crazy?! No way!
ماذا؟ أأنت أحمق؟ هذا مستحيل
Then I'll take care of you too, so quit moaning!
إذًا سأعتني بالأمر لذا الزمي الصمت
I don't wanna see your arms being torn apart! Stop!
لا أريد رؤية يداك وهما تتمزق لذا توقف
Don't be so unreasonable!
كفّي عن هذا
I'm...
...أنا
not gonna die in a place like this!
لن أموت في مكان كهذا
No!
كلا
Crap. I made a ton, like I always do.
بئسًا، أعددتُ كمية كبيرة كما كنتُ أفعل دائمًا
I don't think Pudding-chan will eat this much.
لا أظن أنّ بودينغ-تشان ستأكل كل هذا
What am I thinking?
بماذا كنتُ أفكر؟
Oh, well, if she can't finish it, I'll eat it.
حسنًا، إن لم تستطع إكماله، فسآكل معها
Whoa! You made a lot!
لقد أعددت الكثير
But I can't eat this much.
لا يمكنني أكل كل هذا
Why don't you have some, too?
ما رأيك أن تأكل معي يا سانجي-سان؟
Open your mouth.
افتح فمك
That'd be so nice!
ما أروعه من شعور
Pudding-chan, here I come.
بودينغ-تشان، أنا قادم إليك
Are you going somewhere-nasu ?
هل ستذهب لمكان ما-ناسو؟
Yes, I'm going to get comforted by my only ray of light in this world.
أجل، سأذهب لأنفّه عن نفسي مع بصيص الأمل المتبقي لي
Then do you want this eggplant-nasu ?
إذًا هل تريد هذه الباذنجانة؟
Maybe later.
ربما لاحقًا
Straw Hat and Cat Burglar are already ours-bon.
أسرنا قُبعة القش والقطة اللصة سلفًا-بون
Give up-bon.
لذا استسلم وحسب-بون
So, what?
ثمّ ماذا؟
Then, let's have it out-bon !
إذًا هات ما لديك-بون
I'm not scared of the minks-bon !
أنا لا أخاف من المينك-بون
I guess you're prepared.
على الأرجح أنّك مستعد سلفًا
That's right. I'm wearing special tights that protect me from Electro-feuille.
هذا صحيح، إنني أرتدي بزّة خاصة تحميني من الإلكترو
I'm gonna sort things out with you here!
سأحسم الأمر بيننا
Big Brothers! It's you guys!
كما توقعت، أنتما أخواي
– What?! You... – Pekoms.
...أنت-غارا - بيكومز -
Big Brother Pedro! Big Brother Zepo!
أخي بيدرو أخي زيبو
Garchu!
غارتشو
Garchu...
...غارتشو
Why are you here?
لِمَ أنت هنا؟
I'm a member of the Big Mom Pirates now.
أنا عضو بطاقم بيغ مام
– You'll lose more than an eye this time!
ستخسر أكثر من عينك هذه المرّة - ستخسر أكثر من عينك هذه المرّة  -
That was close-bon !
كان ذلك وشيكًا-بون
My left eye still twitches sometimes-feuille.
لا زالت عيني اليسرى توخزني أحيانًا - فويل
I remember the pain of getting stabbed by you-toilette !
إني أتذكر الألم الناجم من طعنك لي-توالي
I remember too, of course.
وأنا أتذكر ذلك أيضًا
Look what you've done, you thieves.
انظرا ماذا فعلتما أيّها اللصان
W-What the...
...ما الذي
Big Bro!
أخي
I'm taking 100 years of your life!
سآخذ 100 سنة من حياتك
Stay with me, Zepo!
زيبو، تماسك
Zepo...
...زيبو
Zepo!
زيبو
Big Brother Zepo!
أخي زيبو
There wasn't enough for 100 years.
لم يكن في حياته 100 سنة
He only had 30 years to live.
لم يكن أمامه سوى 30 سنة ليعيشها
Since you're his partner, I need you to pay the rest.
يجب أن تدفع الباقي بصفتك شريكه
Now, give me 70 years' worth of your soul!
أعطني الـ70 سنة الباقية
Please, Mama! He's like a big brother to me!
أتوسل إليكِ يا ماما لقد كان كأخي الكبير
If you take 70 years, Big Bro Pedro will die too!
إن أخذتي منه 70 سنة، فسيموت هو أيضًا
Stop, Pekoms. That's pathetic-bon.
توقف يا بيكومز، هذا مثير للشفقة-بون
I'm begging you, Mama!
أتوسل إليكِ يا ماما
Pekoms...
...بيكومز
Stop crying, Pekoms! All right.
توقف عن البكاء يا بيكومز، لقد فهمت
10 years. I'll knock off 10 years.
عشرة سنوات، سأنقص من المجموع 10 سنوات
What?!
ماذا؟
But you took away an eye from Tamago, and that's serious.
ولكنك سلبت عين تاماغو، وتلك فعلة شنعاء
I'll take 60 years of your life!
سآخذ 60 سنة من حياتك
Aren't you satisfied, Pekoms?
أيرضيك هذا يا بيكومز؟
W-Well...
...هـ-هذا
Hey, Big Mom!
يا بيغ مام
How many years will you spare for this?
كم سنة ستتنازلين عنها مقابل هذه؟
Big Bro!
أخي
It's pointless to die here! The day of the new dawn is coming!
لا فائدة من الموت هنا، ففجر العالم قد اقتَرَب
I must go back to my country!
يجب أن أعود إلى موطني
You're so handsome.
أنت وسيم للغاية
I'll reduce it to 50 years.
سأجعلها 50 سنة
Go on with your life.
امضِ في حياتك
Legs Benedict!
ليغ بينيديكت
Say it-bon, Pedro! Why did you come back?!
أجبني يا بيدرو، لِمَ عُدت إلى هنا؟
To this nightmarish island where your partner got killed and 50 years of your life was taken away!
ما الذي عاد بك إلى هذه الجزيرة المشؤومة التي لقي فيها شريكك حتفه وسُلِبت منك فيها 50 سنة؟
The Straw Hats saved my homeland, and I'm indebted to them!
،لقد قام طاقم قبعة القش بإنقاذ موطني وأنا هنا لرد الدين لهم
On top of that, I believe they're the ones who will lead the world to the new dawn!
والأهم من ذلك، أؤمن أنّهم يومًا ما سيقودون العالم إلى فجرٍ جديد
Pedro!
بيدرو
The new dawn is close!
سيبزغ فجر العالم قريبًا
In time, the Straw Hats will surpass you people and change the world!
سيتفوقون عليكم وسيغيرون العالم
They can't do anything! Where do you think you are-bon ?!
ليس بيدهم حيلة، أين تخال نفسك-بون؟
This is Whole Cake Island-bon !
نحن في جزيرة الكعكة الكاملة-بون
Does that matter?
ثمّ ماذا؟
I believe in the Straw Hats.
أنا أثق في طاقم قبعة القش
That's why I'm happy to spend the short remainder of my life...
...لهذا أنا سعيد لتقديم ما تبقى من حياتي
helping them!
من أجلهم
But don't get me wrong.
ولكن إياك أن تسيء فهمي
I'm not gonna die here!
فأنا لن أموت هنا
They haven't fulfilled their reason for being here yet!
فهم لم يحصلوا على مبتغاهم في هذه الجزيرة بعد
I'm not gonna die yet.
لن أموت الآن
Please. You let me through earlier.
دعيني أدخل من فضلك
No means no, silly boy.
ألا تفهم معنى لا أيها الولد الأحمق؟
But why?
ولكن لماذا؟
Madam Pudding is currently busy: B-U-S-Y.
بودينغ-ساما مشغولةٌ حاليًّا مـ-ـشـ-ـغـ-ـو-لـ-ـه
"Busy"?
مشغولة؟
I'll kick your butt, silly boy. Go away, silly boy.
سأطردك أيها الولد الأحمق، ارحل أيها الولد الأحمق
Wait a minute...
...لحظة
I think there's a veranda outside her room.
أتذكر وجود شرفة لغرفة بودينغ-تشان
I can hand it in through the window.
سأسلمها لها من خلال النافذة
Maybe I shouldn't do this. I'll look like a creep.
ربما لا يفترض بي هذا، فقد أبدو كمن يتلذذ باختلاس النظر
Well... we'll be husband and wife tomorrow!
لا يهم، فنحن سنصبح زوجين غدًا
So, even if she's changing...
...لذا حتّى وإن كانت تغيّر ملابسها
Or e-e-even if she's naked, there's nothing wrong with it!
و-و-وحتّى وإن كانت عارية، فلن تكون جريمة
Good. She's laughing.
هذا مطمئن، ضحكتها يدل على أنّها بخير
There she is. Pudding-chan !
ها هي بودينغ-تشان
Who is she talking to?
إلى من تتحدث؟
Reiju?!
ريجو؟
Why is she here?
لِمَ هي هنا؟
What does she want from Pudding-chan ?
ماذا تريد من بودينغ-تشان؟
You must be dreaming! Me, marry that lowlife?!
توقفي عن هذه الأحلام أنا أتزوج ذلك الوضيع؟
Definitely not!
هذا مستحيل
I'm Mama's favorite. Especially when it comes to my acting skill.
أنا المفضلة لدى ماما، خصوصًا مهاراتي في التمثيل
She cares about me so much, that it can really get annoying sometimes.
إنّها تكترث بأمري كثيرًا هذه الأيام لدرجة أنني ضجرتُ من هذا
It isn't hard for me to keep her happy, since I can easily manipulate any man.
كم يسهل عليّ خداع رجل من أجل أن أبقي ماما سعيدة
Tricking the Straw Hats was a piece of cake, too.
خداع طاقم قبعة القش كان سهلًا أيضًا
Only my family knows my true nature.
عائلتي فقط هي من تعرف حقيقتي
That little...!
...تلك اللعينة
Man, he won't shut up.
بحقّك، ألن تخرس؟
Damn... that Pudding!
بودينغ اللعينة
Luffy, stop! They're really gonna be torn apart!
توقف يا لوفي ستتمزق يداك حقًّا
I'll make her pay...
...سأجعلها
no matter what!
تدفع الثمن حتمًا
So, don't worry.
لذا لا تقلقا
I'm not going to marry him.
فأنا لن أتزوجه
Listen.
اسمعا
I'm not going to marry him, because...
...لن أتزوجه، لأنّ
he's an idiot that played right into my hands by falling for me...
ذلك الأحمق فريسة سهلة وقد وقع في مكيدتي
and because he's going to be shot in the middle of the ceremony...
...وسأرديه قتيلًا بيدي
by me.
خلال مراسم الزفاف
And you guys aren't going to survive, either.
كما أننا لن ندعكم أحياءًأ
Hey, wait, Pudding!
مهلًا لحظة يا بودينغ
What are you talking about?!
ما الذي تقولينه؟
Goodbye.
وداعًا
You pathetic rats.
أيها الفئران المثيران للشفقة
She was planning to set us up from the beginning!
لقد كانت تخدعنا منذ البداية
What did Sanji ever do to her?! Dammit!
لِمَ تحمل الضغينة تجاه سانجي بالأساس؟ سحقًا
You people are so naive!
أنتم ساذجون
The evil army Germa 66?
جيش جيرما 66 الشرير؟
Stay in your fantasy world, you dumbasses!
عيشوا عالمكم الخيالي أيها الحمقى
All Mama wanted was your army of clone soldiers...
لقد كان هدف ماما منذ البداية هو إحكام قبضتها
and your advanced technology!
على جيش الجنود المستنسخين والتقنية العلمية التي بحوزتكم
You're so obnoxious.
ما أبغضك
My, aren't you defiant.
عجبًا، يا لكِ من جريئة
That side of you means you won't obey us, which is why we don't need you.
نحن نعرف أنّكم لن تطيعونا، ولسنا بحاجة لطاعتكم
The entirety of Germa is anchored in our territory right now.
فمملكة جيرما بأكملها متواجدة في منطقتنا حاليًّا
You guys are nothing more than flies
لقد استدرجناكم كالذباب عن طريق قطعة حلوى لذيذة وهذه القطعة هي زواج سانجي السياسي
Well done.
أحسنتم
It's gone just as Mama planned.
سار كل شيء كما خططت له ماما
At the wedding tomorrow,
...أنتم يا عائلة فينسموك
the entire Vinsmoke family...
...سيُقضى عليكم جميعًا
will be executed!
غدًا في حفلة الزفاف